Katie Zhan

rgzhan@uwaterloo.ca katiezhan.github.io github.com/katiezhan linkedin/in/katiezhan (778) 707-9288

SUMMARY OF QUALIFICATIONS

Self-motivation and proficiency in numerous programming languages displayed through a variety of personal projects.

Collaboration and teamwork skills displayed through placing 3rd in UBC Physics Olympics as a member of Lord Byng's team.

Adaptability and attention to detail developed through 3 years of providing first aid assistance.

Communication and interpersonal skills developed through 3 years of mentorship and 1 year of providing customer service in Domino's.

EXPERIENCE

TELUS World of Science

07/2016

- Mentored ~20 Science World campers ages 10-14 daily
- Acted as a technology summer camp assistant in charge of preparing and leading activities
- Taught campers the fundamentals of Python and Arduino

First Responder with CPR/AED Level HCP 2014 - 2017

- Captain of the First Responder Team of 10 in high school
- Provided over 100 hours of medical care within the community
- Responsible for the wellbeing of all personnel within the school

Big Brothers Big Sisters of Canada

2014-2017

- Mentored children at Queen Elizabeth Elementary weekly
- Supported the children's development through interpersonal communication

EDUCATION

University of Waterloo

Candidate for Bachelor of Computer Science Honours Co-op 2017 - 2022 Currently in 1B

Lord Byng Secondary School

- Scored 5 on AP Computer Science A

2012 - 2017

- Vancouver, B.C.
 - Scored 5 on AP Calculus AB

Graduated with 98% average

PROJECTS

Personal Website

Javascript + HTML + CSS

Designed and built a responsive personal website from scratch that is hosted on GitHub.

Audio Visualizer

Javascript + HTML + CSS

A web application that produces visual representations of the sound waves of inputted files using Web Audio API.

SKILLS

Computer Proficiency:

Java, HTML5, CSS, C, Javascript, Python

Tools and Technologies:

Android Studio, Git, Photoshop, Microsoft Excel

Languages:

English, Mandarin, Japanese

AWARDS & SCHOLARSHIPS

University of Waterloo President's Scholarship of Distinction Admission average of 95%+ 2017

Alice C. Rowe Memorial Award Recognition for character and

contribution to Lord Byng Secondary 2017

District Dogwood Scholarship Recognize graduating B.C. student for excellence in area of interest

B.C. Achievement Scholarship Recognize the top 800 graduates in the province of B.C.

2017

2017